2011getaway.com 2012-02-03

# Privacy Policy Caribbean Cruise line

Caribbean Cruise Line (CRC) Privacy Policy 

  This site is owned and operated by CRC. Here at CRC, we recognize that many visitors to our Site are concerned about both the information they provide to us and how we treat that information. So we've developed the Privacy Policy described below. We may update or change the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check in occasionally. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:   
Caribbean Cruise Line  
PO Box 70038, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33307  
Attn: Caribbean Cruise Getaway Department

Our office is open from 9 a.m. - 5 p.m. Eastern Standard Time, Monday through Friday. Please feel free to e-mail us anytime at [Policy@CaribbeanCL.com](mailto:Policy@CaribbeanCL.com) . We'll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns. 

  Our Policy 

  Caribbean Cruise Line (CRC) respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Site or responds to our interactive advertisements. At our Site, we don't collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless he or she provides it to us voluntarily and knowingly. We don't require you to register or provide information to us in order to view our Site. 

  Why you might furnish personally identifiable information to us.   
If you choose to respond to one of our interactive advertisements or promotions, confirm a reservation online, or make an inquiry through our website, we will need some personally identifiable information to respond. 

  CRC regards all personally identifiable information as confidential and maintains it under strict conditions of security. CRC treats all personally identifiable customer information as confidential business information. CRC has implemented strict security measures intended to prevent an unauthorized third party, such as a hacker, from gaining access to CRC data bases. We regularly monitor access to such information and its use within CRC by its employees to ensure that personally identifiable information is securely maintained and used only as permitted under this privacy policy. When CRC provides personally identifiable information to a third party organization (as discussed below), CRC requires the third party organization to adhere to security requirements comparable to those imposed by CRC, and to use the information only as expressly authorized by us. We regularly monitor the third party organizations to ensure compliance with their contractual commitments to security and proper use.  

How we use personally identifiable information you furnish to us.   
We use personally identifiable information supplied by you ONLY as follows: 

As necessary to respond to your inquiry, and make a record of it. In the email section of our Site, we ask for some personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, and phone number. We use this information only if we need to contact you directly because our attempts to contact you by email were unsuccessful. We may share your personally identifiable information with individual CRC properties in order to reply to your inquiry. As necessary to provide any goods or services, including hotel reservations, that you have specifically requested, and to make records of these transactions. (For example, we would use the information that you provide to mail you a reservation confirmation, or to respond to an email question. This may include providing the necessary information to individual suppliers as necessary to provide the goods or services. To permit CRC or others to provide other information about goods or services that are related to the services that CRC offers. This is called "Marketing Opportunities" in this privacy policy. Marketing Opportunities do not include - and CRC expressly prohibits the companies offering them from using your personally identifiable information for - products or services of theirs other than those CRC has expressly authorized. For inclusion in statistical or demographic profiles that CRC uses for general marketing purposes. Although personally identifiable information is used to compile the profiles, we use the profiles only as aggregate data, without reference to personally identifiable information, or for targeted Marketing Opportunities. 

  You may "opt out" at any time.   
You may notify CRC at any time that you no longer wish to receive Marketing opportunities. You may do so by writing to CRC at   
Caribbean Cruise Line  
Port of Palm Beach, 301 Broadway STE 101B Riviera Beach, FL 33404  
Attention: Marketing Dept. Email Removal 

Or you may telephone CRC at 1-800-221-8200 , or email Remove@Caribbeancl.com with a request to " remove." 

  We limit third party access to personally identifiable information.   
We don't share any personally identifiable information you give us with anyone outside of CRC other than: 

Third party organizations that CRC engages to perform services on CRC's behalf.   
Third party organizations that store data on CRC's behalf.   
Third party organizations that provide Marketing Opportunities.   
When CRC is required by law to do so.  
In CRC's contracts with third party organizations the third party organization may use personally identifiable information collected on our website only for the express purpose permitted by its contract with CRC, which will be consistent with this privacy policy. As noted, CRC's contracts also require each third party organization to maintain all personally identifiable information as confidential under strict security conditions and in accordance with CRC's privacy policy. 

    CRC does not seek children's personally identifiable information.   
CRC does not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from individuals under thirteen years of age. Where appropriate, we will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our websites or advertisements. If a child has voluntarily provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child may contact us at the street address, telephone number, or email address listed above to request that this information deleted from our records. We will use all reasonable efforts to delete the child's personally identifiable information from our data bases, including those maintained by third parties on our behalf. 

  Credit Card Security.   
CRC uses secure socket layer (SSL) technology to process credit card transactions initiated through our Site. SSL is the industry standard for secure e-commerce transactions. It prevents your personally identifiable information from being read by someone else as it travels across the Internet. Among other security measures, all personally identifiable information that you supply in a credit card transaction, including credit card number, name, and address, is encrypted 

    Our use of "cookies" and "pixels."   
Like most companies, we (or third party organizations that we engage) use "cookie" technology on our Site. When you log in, the cookie tells us whether you've visited us before or are a new visitor. The cookie doesn't track any personally identifiable information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer. 

CRC uses transparent GIF files (called "pixels") to help manage online advertising. Ordinarily an advertising management partner provides the pixels. These files enable the advertising partner to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. 

The information that we collect and share using cookies and pixels is anonymous and not personally identifiable by CRC or the advertising partner. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. 

    Traffic Data  
Data about traffic and usage are not personally identifying or identifiable, and are not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. CRC may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form, without any personally identifiable information. CRC provides the aggregated data to third parties for analysis of use of the site. (For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of people visited a certain area on our Web site, or searched Web sites for the term "hotel.") CRC collects some information regarding use of the Services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) that user’s access. For example, CRC's servers collect information about the site from which a user entered to enable CRC to calculate and pay its affiliates, information about the most frequently searched terms to help our advertisers provide the most relevant search results, information about usage to check for fraudulent behavior or other abnormalities, and to ensure that our Services are technically superior. CRC, either itself or with contracted third party service providers, uses the information (in aggregate form, without any personally identifiable information) to improve the Services. 

Third party advertising companies under contract with CRC may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of ads. Any such information is anonymous, without any personally identifiable information. The advertisers may use this anonymous information about users' visits to this and other sites to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest. No personally identifiable information is collected during this process. The information is anonymous and does not link online actions to an identifiable person. 

  Changes in the privacy policy.   
CRC reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time. We will post advance notice of any change on our Site. We will apply any change prospectively only; any information that you have submitted prior to the change will be used and disclosed only as permitted by the privacy policy then in effect.
